他们曾经是金融大鳄
They once top the world
直到金融危机来袭  他们销声匿迹
until the financial crisis strike they flamed out.
于是他们的妻子夺过了掌控权
That's when their wives got busy taking over.
华尔街之妻
the wives of wall street.
佩内洛普  时尚显贵
Penelope, the fashion mogul.
你穿我的设计真是太美了
You look amazing in my dress.
玛格  化妆品女王
Margo,the cosmetics queen.
你要不是我儿子  我肯定炒掉你
If you weren't my son, I'd fire your ass.
柯莱特  家庭装饰大牌
Colette, home decor diva.
今天要冲销售量  各位
Let's sell today people.
当然了  还有汉娜  她接下来会做什么
And then of course, there's Hannah. What will she do next?
别让任何人阻止你
Don't let anyone stop you
得到自己想要的
from getting what you want.
不  不  不
No, no, no.
汉娜的镜头要多一点
We need more Hannah.
她是我们高收视的原因
She's the reason our numbers are spiking.
电视节目就是这样  彼得
We all like this at the network, Peter.
讲究平衡
It's balanced.
也许你那些令人麻痹的金融节目是这样
Maybe that works for your brain-numbing finance shows.
但这是真人秀
But this is reality tv.
要的就是激化冲突
We need to hype the conflict.
要的就是意料之外
We need the unexpected.
抱歉打扰下  门罗先生
Uh, sorry to interrupt Mr. Monroe.
警方打电话找你
The police are calling for you.
有桩凶杀案
There's been a murder.
好了  心形的袖扣
Okay. Heart-shaped cuff links?
你别再猜了好吗
Could you stop guessing?
好吧  小马  火箭
Okay, a pony? It's a rocket.
乔治·卢卡斯签名的限量版
It's a limited-edition "Star Wars" Lightsaber
《星球大战》光剑
signed by George Lucas.
是啊  星战玩具最能表达
Yes, because nothing says "Happy valentine's day"
"情人节快乐"
like a "Star wars" toy.
等等  等等
Wait. Wait, wait, wait.
拜托你不要告诉我  咱们第一个情人节
Please tell me that you didn't get me a lightsaber
你要送我星战光剑
for our first valentine's day together.
对我有点信心好吗
Please give me some credit.
我送你的你肯定会喜欢
You are gonna love what I got you.
我送你的你也肯定会喜欢
And you're gonna love what I got you.
你呢  埃斯波
What about you, Espo?
明天的情人节有安排吗
Any plans for valentine's day tomorrow?
有
Uh, yeah.
调查凶杀案
Investigating a murder.
明白了
I see.
被害人是汉娜·格林  23岁
Victim is Hannah Green, 23.
她是《华尔街之妻》里的明星
She's one of the stars of the show "The wives of wall street."
他哥哥正从新泽西往警局赶
Her brother's on his way into the precinct from Jersey.
《华尔街之妻》那个真人秀吗
"Wives of wall street," The reality show?
对  你看过吗
Yeah. Seen it?
看了一会儿我就想自杀了
Just long enough to make me want to kill myself.
一群失心疯互相背后捅刀子  一分钟都受不了
One minute of lunatics backstabbing each other is enough.
说到背后捅刀子
Speaking of backstabbing...
她看上去像是睡着了
She almost looks like she's asleep.
昨晚11点15分路过的公车司机
The bus driver who came through last night
也以为她是睡了
11:15 thought she was.
今天早上才有人发现她死了
It wasn't until this morning anyone realized she was dead.
鉴于肝脏温度
Based on liver temp,
死亡时间最早是10点至10点半
the earliest she could've died is 10:00, 10:30.
她是那个时间段被杀害的
Okay, so she was killed in that hour.
看来是这样的
Looks that way.
没有发现皮包和手机
There's no purse or cell on the body.
如果是劫杀
But if she was mugged,
歹徒没看到她右手腕上的钻石手镯
the doer missed that diamond tennis bracelet on her right wrist.
如果是抢劫犯
And if it was a mugger,
那他对刀具的品味相当讲究
he has exquisite taste in cutlery.
这是高原牌VG大厨刀
That's a Takahara V.G. Chef knife.
一把大概要两百块
Runs about 200 bucks.
好高档的凶器啊
That's pretty high-end for a murder weapon.
无论是谁袭击了她
Well, whoever attacked her,
她都有反击
it looks she fought back.
她手腕上有自卫伤  擦伤
She has defensive wounds, abrasions on her wrists,
指甲里可能还留有遗传物质
and some possible genetic material underneath her fingernails.
回到验尸房我就会查DNA
I'll run D.N.A. once I get back to the morgue.
她住在这个区吗
She live in the area?
不  她住中心区  汤普森酒店
No, downtown. Thompson hotel.
那么她来这里做什么
So what was she doing up here?
不知道
I don't know.
《华尔街之妻》的制片人说
The producer of "The wives of wall street"
他们没有在这一带拍摄
said they weren't filming in this area.
抱歉我迟到了
Sorry I'm... late.
又是因为珍妮吗
Yeah. Jenny again?
是的
Yeah.
今早她的体温上升[排卵期]
Her temperature spiked this morning,
我临时就得上场
and suddenly it's showtime.
她完全依照科学理论来进行造人运动
She's got this baby making down to a science.
听起来真浪漫啊
Sounds romantic.
我感觉自己像鸡舍里的公鸡
I feel like a rooster in a henhouse.
只不过  那里只有一只母鸡
Except for, there's only one hen--
还是只很专横的母鸡
A very bossy hen.
好了  埃斯波  你和"公鸡"
Okay, Espo, you and the rooster
开始排查
start a canvass,
我和卡塞尔去找制片人
and Castle and I will talk to the producer,
看他能否提供些汉娜的背景情况
see if he can give us any background on Hannah's life.
听着  我不是这样的人
Look, I am not this person.
有些事就是发生了  然后就
Things just happen, and they...
就这样定义了你  但是
they end up defining you, but it's...
这不公平
It's not always fair.
就是这个
That's it.
这是汉娜最后的镜头
That's the last image we shot of Hannah.
可怜的姑娘
Poor girl.
太遗憾了
Such a loss.
她是收视率的王牌
She was ratings gold.
你们要调查清楚是谁做的
You're gonna have to find who did this.
观众们会想要知道的
The audience will want to know.
是啊  更别提她的家人  地检
Yeah, not to mention her family, the D.A...
门罗先生  这是什么时候拍的
Mr. Monroe, when was this shot?
前天  大概晚上八点  怎么了
Day before yesterday, around 8:00 P.M. Why?
因为她尸体被发现时穿的是这身衣服
Because she's wearing the same clothes that we found her in.
那可是整整一天以后了
That's a full day later.
你知不知道拍摄后她去了哪里
Do you know where she went after filming
或是她为什么去曼哈顿西区
or why she would've been on the upper west side?
说实话  摄像机下班
Well, to be honest, when the cameras go away,
我也下班
so do I.
所以我根本不知道她平时做些什么
So I don't even know what she did on her free time.
她在录像里似乎很生气  是什么原因
In the video, she seems upset. Any idea what about?
你们得知道
Oh, you gotta understand,
汉娜是作为佩内洛普的助手进入节目的
we brought Hannah in to be Penelope's assistant.
我们得增加些戏剧化情节
You know, to mix things up a little bit.
小镇姑娘有想做时装设计师的
The small-town girl with the big-time dreams
远大理想
of becoming a fashion designer.
她会在《华尔街之妻》节目中成功吗
Will she make it with the wives of wall street?
她只是在镜头前夸张演出
She's just milking it for the camera.
演员都是这样
They all do.
所以这是完全不真实的真人秀
So it's a reality show, just without the reality.
我倾向于认为这是高于现实
I like to think of it as heightened reality.
有着现实味道的
Reality-ish.
在真正的现实中
In real reality,
她与节目组的人有矛盾吗
did she have problems with anyone on the show?
你把一帮女强人放在一起
Well, you put a bunch of tough-minded women together,
哪有不吵架的
you're gonna get a spat or two.
但汉娜是摄制组家庭的一员
But Hannah was part of the family.
好吧  我需要她所有的影带
Okay, well, I'm gonna need all of her tapes
以防其中有线索
just in case there's something relevant.
没问题
Of course.
不过  你应该查查她真正的家人
Although, you might want to check out her own family.
我知道她跟她哥哥查理·格林关系不好
I know that she had trouble with her brother--Charlie Green.
汉娜总想在大城市一举成名
Hannah always wanted to make it big in the city,
她来到这里时
and when she came here, she, uh,
她迷失了方向
she lost her way.
我本该多做点什么
I should've done more.
我是她哥哥  我本该保护她的
I was her brother. I should've protected her.
格林先生
Mr. Green,
你最后一次跟汉娜说话是什么时候
when was the last time you talked to Hannah?
几天前
Uh, a few days ago.
我打给她  吵了起来
I called her. We fought.
吵什么
About what?
还是那些事
The usual.
她就那么把自己的生活
About how she was putting her life out there
袒露在全世界面前
for the world to see,
这样会对这个家造成的影响
what it was doing to the family.
她
She...
她说我不理解
She said I didn't understand,
这里面的内幕远比我知道的多
that there was more going on than I knew.
但对我来说  很简单  她需要回家
But to me, it was simple-- she needed to come home.
这么说  你并不赞成她
So... you didn't approve of her
上《华尔街之妻》吗
being on "the wives of wall street"?
赞同
Approve?
不  我们难过死了
No, it was killing us...
看她做的那些选择  看她过着不堪的生活
To see the choices she made, the way she was living her life,
一切都被录下来全国播放
all of it out there on national television.
那还是在她跟人搞外遇之前
And that was before she started having the affair.
外遇
Affair?
你睡了我老公  还腆着脸回来工作
You screw my husband, you think you're welcome here?
他选择了我  佩内洛普
He chose me, penelope.
接受现实吧
Deal with it.
我不会放过你的
I am coming for you.
这么说被害人跟真人秀中
So our victim was sleeping with the husband
另一个女人的丈夫上床了吗
of one of the other women in the show?
不仅是上床
Not just sleeping with.
被佩内洛普抓奸之后
Hannah and Bob moved in together
汉娜和鲍勃同居了
after Penelope found out about them.
可是节目制作人却只字未提
And yet the show's pducer said nothing about it.
要我说他是为了保全自己
I'd say he was covering his own asset.
这场外遇在全国播放
This affair was broadcast on national television.
他真以为我们不会发现吗
Did he really think that we weren't gonna find out about it?
我的天
Oh, my goodness.
是佩内洛普干的  对吧
It was Penelope, wasn't it?
汉娜那样破坏她的婚姻
Well, after what Hannah did to her marriage,
真不忍责怪她
I wouldn't blame her.
是这样  鲍勃失业后
See, Penelope kept her family afloat
是佩内洛普赚钱养家
after Bob lost his job,
然后她给了汉娜一个大好机会
and then she gives Hannah this--this big break,
而汉娜回报她的方式
and then Hannah repays her
就是跟她无能的丈夫搞到一起
by screwing her worthless excuse of a husband.
你是《华尔街之妻》的粉丝吗
You're a fan of "Wives of wall street"?
当然了  这是最棒的真人秀  怎么了
Oh, yeah. It's the best show on TV. Why?
没什么  我只是以为像你这样的女人
I don't--I just assumed that a woman like you
会喜欢更加...深奥的精神食粮
would prefer more... sophisticated fare.
你说什么
Excuse me?
你刚说什么
W-what did you just say?
蕾妮  什么事
Hey, Lanie. What's up?
我给你发了一张指甲碎片的图片
I'm sending you a picture of a fingernail fragment
是从被害人的头皮中拔出的
I pulled from the victim's scalp.
我猜是凶手在袭击时留下的
I figured it came from the killer during the attack.
你能查下DNA吗
Can you run D.N.A.?
已经在做了
It's already happening.
好的  谢谢
Great. Thank you.
埃斯波西托  是我看错了还是...
'sito, is it just me or...
这两个颜色是不是完全一致
Is that a perfect match?
等一等
Okay, wait a minute.
你们过度解读了
You're reading too much into this.
至少等到我们拍摄完毕好吗
Can you at least wait until we're done filming?
-我并没有  -还真是优雅的说法
- I am not having-- - What a classy thing to say.
天啊  你不知道我多认真
Oh, my-- you don't know how I meant it.
-她又不是故意的  -我没那意思
- Like she did it on purpose? - I'm not saying that.
我们不会取消婚礼
Well, we're not canceling the wedding.
我只是说这一切糟透了  好吗
Look, I'm just saying that this sucks, okay?
汉娜居然在我们婚礼前一个月去世了
Hannah dying a month before our wedding...
-亲爱的  -阿什莉说得对
- Hush, darling. - Ashley's right.
或许我们应该延期之类的
Maybe we should, like, postpone it or something.
延期
Postpone?
就为了那个贱人
For that bitch?
佩内洛普
Penelope!
听着  又不是我杀了她
Look, it's not like I killed her.
打扰一下  福斯特女士
Excuse me, Ms. Foster.
我是贝克特警探  纽约警察
Detective Beckett, NYPD.
你好吗
How do you do?
我很好
I'm fine.
但是你
Uh, but you...
要被逮捕了
are under arrest
罪名是谋杀汉娜·格林
for the murder of Hannah Green.
所以我猜的确是你杀了她
So I guess it is like you killed her.
还在拍摄吗  刚那段拍下来没
Are you still rolling? Did you get that?
你们竟敢在演职人员面前逮捕我
How dare you arrest me in front of the cast and crew.
你该担心的是这个  佩内洛普
You should be more worried about this, Penelope.
这是一份实验室报告
That's a lab report
关于在汉娜头发里发现的指甲碎片
for a fingernail fragment found in Hannah's hair.
DNA检测结果与你吻合
It's a D.N.A. Match to you.
你想说说它是怎么到那里去的吗
You want to tell me how it got there?
因为要是你不说
Because if you won't,
我肯定你丈夫鲍勃会说的
I'm sure your husband Bob will.
鲍勃  得了吧
Bob? Come on.
你以为他会跟你说什么
What do you think he's gonna tell you?
那个混蛋是个蠢货
That poor bastard is so stupid
他还以为汉娜对他有真感情
He thought Hannah actually had feelings for him.
而大家都知道她想要的
And everybody knew all she wanted to do
是提高在节目中的关注度
was up her profile on the show.
她只是在利用他
She was just using him.
那是真爱
It was true love.
汉娜和我相爱了
Hannah and I were in love.
我们知道你的妻子佩内洛普和汉娜打了一架
Well, we know your wife Penelope and Hannah had a fight.
最近他们之间的战争升级了吗
Had things been escalating between them lately?
汉娜和我从不谈论佩内洛普
Hannah and I never talked about Penelope.
但是你跟汉娜同居
But you lived with Hannah.
你知道她昨晚去了哪里吗
Do you know where she was last night?
不
No.
她昨晚没回家
She didn't come home last night
我昨天一整天都没见到她
and I didn't see her all day yesterday.
那很反常吗
Was that unusual?
对  我很担心
Yeah, I was worried.
但是你真觉得佩内洛普会杀了她吗
But do you really think penelope could killed her?
我当然想杀她
Hell, yeah, I wanted to kill her.
但是当着全美人民的面吗
But with all of America watching?
你以为我有多蠢
How stupid do you think I am?
那指甲是怎么回事
What about the fingernail?
事实是
The truth is...
汉娜跟我确实有些争执
Hannah and I did have a little dustup.
但不是在她被害当晚
But not the night that she was killed.
是前一晚
It was the night before.
那次争执的内容是什么
Okay, so what was the nature of this dustup?
我们在拍摄忏悔场面
We were filming confessionals.
汉娜在摄影棚外等我
Hannah waited for me outside the studio,
说她想谈一谈
said she wanted to talk.
-关于什么  -玛格
- About what? - Margo.
我炒掉汉娜之后玛格雇佣了她
Margo hired Hannah after I fired her ass.
不出意料
And no surprise,
汉娜和玛格在工作上出现了问题
Hannah and Margo were having trouble at work.
尽管听起来很疯狂
And crazy as it sounds,
那个贱人希望我重新雇佣她
that bitch wanted me to rehire her.
你真以为我会相信
Do you actually expect me to believe
她毁了你的婚姻
that she asked you for her job back
却又来求你再雇她吗
after she ruined your marriage?
你以为我为什么会失控
Why do you think I lost it?
我扯了她的头发  弄坏了指甲
I yanked her hair and broke my nail.
但仅此而已
But that was it.
她挣脱走人了
She broke free, took off,
那是我最后一次见到汉娜
and that was the last I saw of Hannah.
你不介意我问下昨晚
And I suppose you won't mind me asking
10点15至11点15你在哪里吧
where you were between 10:15 and 11:15 last night?
诺合体育馆的跆拳道老师
Okay, so the kickboxing teacher at Noho gym
证实佩内洛普十点到十一点
confirms that Penelope was "sweating her ass off"
在市区一个教学班"挥汗如雨"
downtown in a class from 10:00 till 11:00.
所以杀害汉娜的凶手
So whoever killed Hannah,
并非佩内洛普·福斯特
it wasn't Penelope Foster.
那好吧  凶器查得怎么样
Okay, then. Where are we on the murder weapon?
没有指纹
You know what? There's no fingerprints.
不过他们在刀柄上
But they did find antimony oxide
找到了氧化锑
on the knife's handle.
没记错的话  这是阻燃剂
A fire retardant if memory serves.
从伤口情况看来
And also, based on the wound,
这把刀应该是新的  或者从没使用过
it looks like the knife was new or had never been used.
伙计们  来看这个
Hey, guys. Check this out.
一个粉丝拍了这张照片
A fan took this and posted it
然后传到《华尔街之妻》粉丝网上
to a "Wives of Wall Street" fan site
是案发当晚
The night of the murder.
这是汉娜
That's Hannah.
照片有时间戳
Yeah, and it was time stamped.
这是她被害前二十分钟拍的
This is 20 minutes before she was killed.
二十分钟
20 minutes?
这栋楼一定和她的凶杀案有关系
So that building must have something to do with the murder.
知道在哪吗
Uh, any idea where it is?
照片没有位置信息
The photo wasn't geotagged,
但能看到这栋楼的门牌号以46结尾
but you can see part of the building's number ends in 46.
我知道谁住这里
And I can tell you who lives here.
我认识这栋楼
I know this building.
是真人秀里的
It's from the show.
这是玛格家  在上西区某处
This is Margo's place, somewhere on the upper west.
83街以南
South of 83rd.
等等  也就是说玛格就住在汉娜
Wait. That means Margo lives right around the corner
死亡现场不远处
from where Hannah was killed.
我妈妈在打电话
My mom's just wrapping up a call,
她马上就出来  等她
but she'll be right out, as soon as s--
我回头再跟你说  我来了
I will talk to you later. Here I am.
谢谢  亲爱的
Thank you, sweetheart.
有什么事吗
How can I help you?
我们就是想理清
Uh, we just needed to go over
汉娜死前24小时都做了些什么
the last 24 hours of Hannah's life.
我们想知道
And we were wondering,
你最后一次见她是什么时候
when was it that you last saw her?
她昨晚十点过来待了几分钟  怎么了
She came by around 10:00 last night for a few minutes. Why?
她走后  就在离这里不远处被杀了
Because she was killed around the corner from here just after leaving.
太可怕了
That's terrible.
的确
Yes, yes, it is.
介意告诉我们她来干什么吗
Um, would you mind telling us why she came by?
道歉
To apologize.
为什么道歉
For what?
佩内洛普因为外遇的事炒了汉娜之后
After Penelope fired Hannah for the affair,
我聘请她和我儿子斯通一起
I hired her to develop a clothing line
发展一个服装系列
with my son Stone.
我听说她很有天赋
I heard she had talent and...
能多争取些上镜机会也不错
It wouldn't hurt to get some screen time.
鲍勃和汉娜的外遇事件
Bob and Hannah's affair has been
过去几个月一直被大肆报道
the big story arc these past few months.
三天前  她本该过来
Three days ago, she was supposed to come by
介绍她的理念
and present her ideas.
《华尔街之妻》的团队
The "Wives of Wall Street" cameras
都过来准备拍摄了
were here and ready to roll,
汉娜却没有出现
and Hannah's a no-show.
她解释原因了吗
Did she say why?
没有
No.
要是别人的话  我早开除了
If it was anyone else, I would fire her.
但能多争取些上镜机会也不错
But it didn't hurt that you got a little more screen time.
我知道这很俗
I know that's crass,
可这行就是这样的
but that's how this works.
汉娜那晚过来
When she came that night,
只说自己很抱歉
Hannah only said she was sorry
并且答应会好好工作
and promised to recommit to her job.
她说接着要去哪了吗
Did she tell you where she was going afterwards?
没有  我以为
No. I-I assumed that...
她会回家的
she was going home.
她走后你做什么了
And what did you do when she left?
我跟我的娱乐律师电话会议
I jumped on a conference call with my entertainment attorney
讨论斯通和阿什莉的资产分配
to discuss Stone and Ashley's spin-off.
电话记录证实玛格确实
So phone records confirm that Margo made
在10点23分用她的固定电话给她的娱乐律师
a 56-minute phone call to her entertainment lawyer
打了一通长达56分钟的电话
at 10:23 from her landline at the apartment.
其实任何订阅
You know, the truth is anyone who subscribes
《华尔街之妻》网站的人
to the "Wives of Wall Street" web site
都能从照片看出汉娜在玛格家
would've know that Hannah was at Margo's building from that photo.
有新东西发布  网站会发短信提醒你
They send out text alerts any time there's a new post.
有几十万人订阅了这网站
And they have hundreds of thousands of subscribers.
我这儿有个神秘事件
Hey. I got a little mystery here.
你是说除了你的情人节计划吗
You mean besides your Valentine's Day plans?
汉娜的财政状况
Hannah's financials.
过去两个月
For the past two months,
她每周都会存五千美元现金
she's been making weekly cash deposits of 5 grand.
我问过她的家人  还有真人秀里的人
Now I checked with her family, everyone on the show.
都不知道钱是哪来的
No one knows where it's coming from.
应该不是卖女童子军饼干赚来的吧
I take it she didn't make it selling girl scout cookies.
也许跟她没去向玛格介绍
Well, maybe it has something to do with where she was
服装系列的理念那天去的地方有关
when she missed the pitch meeting with Margo on her fashion line.
信用卡记录显示当时她在布鲁克林
Credit card charge puts her at a dive bar
一家叫最后一站的酒吧
in Brooklyn called the Last Stop.
酒吧  她为什么去那里
A dive bar? What was she doing there
而不是出席她人生中最重要的一次会议
instead of at the most important meeting of her life?
不清楚  酒保说她和某个男人
I don't know. The bartender said she was having
聊得热火朝天
a pretty heated discussion with some dude,
于是我请酒保来帮素描师给那个人画像
so I got the bartender sitting down with a sketch artist.
看我们能否查出是谁
See if we can figure out who he is.
抱歉
Uh, sorry.
我得回家...
I had to run home and, uh...
造人
Cock-a-doodle-doo?
说得好
That's good.
没错
Uh, yeah.
明天将会是有史以来最不浪漫的情人节
Tomorrow's going to be the least romantic Valentine's Day ever.
谢了
Oh, thank you.
我让技术人员查了汉娜死前的24小时
So I had tech look into Hannah's last 24 hours,
就是和佩内洛普吵架之后
after her fight with Penelope
去玛格家之前的活动
and before showing up at Margo's.
有什么有用的线索吗
And did they find anything useful?
完全没有
They didn't find anything at all.
她没打电话
She didn't make any calls,
没接电话  没发短信
didn't answer any calls, sent no texts.
甚至没有登录电邮
She didn't even log on to her e-mail
或其他在线账号
or any other online accounts.
完全没有使用电子设备的痕迹
No digital fingerprint whatsoever.
就好像凭空消失了一样
Well, it's like she disappeared.
她怎么会24小时不用电子设备呢
Why would she go radio silent for 24 hours?
她到底上哪去了
And where the hell was she?
我来告诉你们她上哪去了
I'll tell you where she was--
马达加斯加
Madagascar.
就是位于非洲
As in the country
东南海岸的那个国家
off the southeastern coast of Africa,
因有爱动画电影而出名的那个
made famous by the adorable animated film?
没错  我在她指甲里找到的物质
Yep. The material I found underneath her fingernails--
不是凶手的皮肤组织
not skin from an attacker.
而是亚龙木
It's alluaudia.
亚龙木是什么
And what is alluaudia?
一种珍稀多刺的植物
A rare spiny plant
主要生长于马达加斯加
cultivated primarily in Madagascar.
那又是怎么跑到她指甲里去的
So how did it get under her fingernails?
问倒我了
Beats me.
至于她的自卫伤
As for her defensive wounds,
不是临死前留下的
they were not sustained at the time of murder.
而是24小时之前
They're from 24 hours prior.
那差不多是她消失的那段时间
That's about the time that she went off the grid,
两者之间一定有联系
which means there's gotta be a connection.
必须有
Oh, I think there is.
记得这个擦伤吗
Remember this abrasion?
记得
Yeah.
我知道这是怎么搞的了
Well, I figured out what caused it.
她的钻石手链
Her diamond tennis bracelet.
但是那个不是戴在
But wasn't that...
右手吗
on her right wrist?
好记性
Good memory.
所以说她的手是被绑在一起了
So her wrists were tied together.
紧紧地绑了好几个小时
Tight and for several hours.
这就说得通了
Now it's making sense--
第二天还穿着一样的衣服
wearing the same clothes overnight...
消失的一整天
The radio silence...
自卫伤口是在死亡前24小时造成的
And the defensive wounds 24 hours prior to death.
汉娜是被绑架了
Hannah was held hostage.
如果她被绑架了
If Hannah was being held hostage,
她怎么没报案呢
then why didn't she report it?
她又是怎么神奇地跑到马达加斯加去了
And how did she get magically transported to Madagascar?
她为什么要去玛格那为旷工而道歉
And why would she go afterwards to Margo's to apologize for missing work?
一定和那些五千块的存款
It has to have something to do with those $5,000 payments
和在布鲁克林酒吧与神秘男人会面有关
and that meeting with that mystery man at the bar in Brooklyn.
看起来毫无关联
It all seems so random.
我知道在最后
I mean, I know by the end of this,
这些线索都会完美地凶残地联系在一起
all of these clues will fit together beautifully in a murderous mosaic.
但是怎么联系上的呢
But... how?
等等
Wait.
这是你送我的情人节礼物吗
Is this your Valentine's Day gift to me,
一桩毫无头绪的复杂而神秘的案子
a complex mystery where nothing makes sense?
你真是太了解我了
You know me so well.
我真不想打扰你们的爱的交流
Um, I hate to interrupt your little, uh, love connection.
不过我查了交通摄像头
but I checked traffic cameras.
找到汉娜打车到玛格家的录像
I found footage of Hannah arriving at Margo's building in a taxi.
记下出租车牌照
I got the medallion.
联系了司机  他的记录显示
I talked to the cabbie, whose log showed
汉娜是在78大道和莱克星敦街交界处上车的
that the he picked up Hannah at 78th and Lex.
他说了她是从哪出来的吗
Did he say where she was coming from--
是家里  还是店里
Building, store?
他不知道
He didn't know.
他说她招手让他停车时就站在街角
He said that she was standing on the corner when she flagged him down.
她可能是从任何地方出来
Well, then she could've come from anywhere.
我们没办法缩小这个范围
There's no way we can narrow that down, bro.
也许有办法哦
Maybe there is.
我找到一个农业部的负责人
I spoke to a regulator at the department of agriculture.
亚龙木多用于绿色可持续型建筑
It seems Alluaudia is used in green sustainable architecture
毯子  地板和壁纸什么的
in rugs, flooring, wallpaper,
可能就是那附近的哪栋建筑
possibly from a building nearby.
埃斯波  你带警员去排查
Espo, you get uniforms to canvass the area
78大道和莱克星敦街附近
around 78th and Lex
看看有没有绿色可持续型建筑
and see if there's any green sustainable buildings
用到亚什么的树
that might use that allu-- whatever the plant is.
好的
As you wish.
盖茨警监
Captain Gates,
参与案子  忙于不着边际的推测
participating in the case, engaging in idle speculation--
我们挺像的嘛  你和我
we are not so different, you and I.
有一些不同
There's... there's a difference.
我们不一样
We're different.
知道吗  这可能会是重要突破点
You know, this could actually be our big break,
如果我没在那张照片上
only we may not have gotten to it
认出玛格的住处  也许就发现不了
if I hadn't recognized Margo's building in that photo,
所以我觉得你们每个人
which is why I think each of you
今晚都应该看看《华尔街之妻》
should watch some "Wives of Wall Street" episodes tonight--
为了案子
for the good of the case.
想去我家一起看吗
So... would you like to come over for a little viewing party?
好给你机会缠着我问情人节礼物吗
So you can badger me about what I'm getting you for Valentine's Day?
不了  我还是不去了
No, thanks. I think I will pass.
不过我要警告你
Okay, but I'm warning you,
我对送礼挺好胜的
I'm kind of competitive when it comes to giving gifts.
如果你的礼物没我的好  别伤心
Don't feel bad if yours isn't as good as mine.
如果比你的好呢
What if it's better?
比我的好
Better?
怎么可能会比我好
How could it possibly be better?
取决于你会送我什么
Oh, I guess it just depends on what you got me.
理查德  这简直太美了
Oh, Richard. These are breathtaking.
贝克特肯定会喜欢的  老爸
Beckett is going to love them, Dad.
是吧
Right?
想要和这个比  她可要费点心思啊
She'll have a tough time competing with that.
这就是和礼物忍者谈恋爱的苦恼啊
One of the perils of dating a gift ninja.
想成为真正的忍者吗
Ooh, you want to be a real ninja?
只要趁她不注意时放进她大衣口袋
You just slip these into her coat pocket when she's not looking.
妈妈  我喜欢这个主意  出其不意
Mother, I like that idea. The element of surprise.
忍者的手法
The ninja way.
你呢  阿丽克西斯  和麦克斯约好了吗
What about you, Alexis? Any plans with Max?
我们准备一起学习就好了
Uh, we're just going to study together.
听起来和平时没什么两样
Doesn't sound very special.
我想大多数时间会研究对方的眼睛
Well, I think we'll mostly just study each other's eyes.
你呢  妈妈  有什么安排吗
And you, mother, any special plans?
我们准备在我工作室演读《情书》
We're gonna do dramatic readings of "Love letters" at my studio.
很好啊
Oh, well, that's nice.
说起戏剧  有人想和我一起看
And speaking of drama, would anyone like to join me
《华尔街之妻》吗
for a screening of "Wives of Wall Street,"
还有爆米花
Popcorn included?
怎么能吃两个小时的午饭  汉娜
2-hour lunches are not acceptable, Hannah.
我们这可是做生意
We're running a business here.
我没去吃饭  是去拿面料样品了
I wasn't at lunch. I was getting fabric samples.
那也不是迟到的理由
That is no excuse for being late.
你可不是还在堪萨斯了  托托
You are not in Kansas anymore, Toto...
给我一枪吧
Shoot me now.
天呐  真希望我那时有这种真人秀
Boy, I wish I'd had these reality shows in my day.
没剧本  表演夸张
No script, overacting,
可以对别人乱吼  多好的演出啊
screaming at everybody-- what a gig.
我新写了一份广告
Now I have written new promo copy.
校对一遍
Proofread it.
你们两个怎么了
So what's going on between you two?
没什么
Nothing.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
你上了她  不是吗  鲍勃
You're sleeping with her, aren't you, Bob?
没有  没有
No. No.
别跟我撒谎
Don't lie to me.
你在搞她  承认吧
You're screwing Hannah! Admit it.
承认啊
Admit it!
对  行了吧
Yes! All right?
对不起
I'm sorry.
他选择了我  佩内洛普  接受现实吧
He chose me, Penelope. Deal with it.
再让我看见你一次
You come near me again,
我就扯断你的喉咙
and I will rip your throat out.
下周预告  玛格的儿子  斯通
Coming up next week-- Margo's son Stone,
在跟他妈妈学习管理家族生意
who's learning the family business from mom,
和柯莱特的女儿阿什莉
and Colette's daughter Ashley,
一名新兴的陶瓷企业家
budding ceramic entrepreneur,
要订婚了
get engaged.
敬请关注  他们的妈妈
Strap in as their moms get busy
准备他们童话般的婚礼
planning their fairy-tale wedding.
接下来请看"鲨鱼池"
Coming up next-- the "Shark pool"
主持人  亿万富翁  麦克·齐里恩
with bad-boy billionaire Mike Chilean.
你得到资助了
You're funded!
天啊  爸爸
Oh, my God, dad.
你还在看啊
You're still watching?
我
I...
屁股都麻了
I can't feel my butt.
我说的就是这个意思
That's exactly what I mean.
汉娜根本就没有机会
Hannah didn't stand a chance.
她是个小地方来的天真的女人
I mean, she's a small-town, naive young woman.
她是在与虎为伴
She was chum to piranhas.
但是看她对付鲍勃的手段
Yeah, but look what she did to Bob.
好吧  好吧
Okay, okay,
你真的觉得她在耍他吗
Do you really think that she played him,
是佩内洛普说的那样吗
that Penelope was right about that?
那姑娘可比别人想的聪明得多
Oh, that girl was smarter than anybody gave her credit for.
我觉得你说的没错
You know what? I think you're right.
你呢  探长
What about you, detective?
昨晚你有没有看《华尔街之妻》
Did you watch "Wives of Wall Street" last night?
看了一集
I watched an episode.
才一集
Just one episode?
简直就像只吃一片薯片
That's like eating one potato chip.
我一般只吃一片薯片
I usually just eat one potato chip.
现在调查进展到哪里了  探长
So what's the status on the canvass, detective?
警方仍在上东区
Uh, uniforms are still making their way
每一栋有亚龙木踪影的大楼
through every building that uses any trace of alluaudia
进行调查
on the upper east side,
还没有发现
so nothing yet.
你们肯定不会相信
Yo. You guys aren't gonna believe this.
我刚拿到与汉娜
The sketch of the guy that Hannah met
在布鲁克林的小餐馆相见的男子画像
in Brooklyn out at that little restaurant just came in.
餐馆有没有人能认出他的身份
Was anyone at the bar able to I.D. him?
不需要他们来认
They didn't need to.
那是麦克·齐里恩
That's Mike Chilean.
那个疯狂的亿万富翁吗
The crazy billionaire?
还是财经频道另一档热播真人秀
And the entrepreneur host of the financial channel's
《鲨鱼池》的企业家主持人
other hit reality TV show-- the "Shark Pool."
汉娜为什么会放弃
So why would Hannah ditch her shot
玛格的服装介绍会
to pitch Margo a clothing line
去一家布鲁克林的小破餐馆见齐里恩
to meet with Chilean at a seedy bar in Brooklyn?
在那个破地方见面是她的主意
Meeting at that dump was her idea.
我个人比较喜欢马戏团餐厅
Me, I'm more of a Le Cirque guy.
不过她说要去人不多的地方
But she said she needed privacy.
干什么
For what?
我们是在上个月的财经频道聚会上认识的
We met last month at a financial channel party.
她
She was...
漂亮又年轻
cute and young.
然后几天前
Then a few days ago,
她突然给我打电话  要求见面
she calls me out of the blue and asked to meet.
这么说是约会吗
So it was a date?
我原本也是这么想的
That's what I thought, yes.
可等我到了那儿
But when I get there...
她摆出了一幅《鲨鱼池》参加者姿态
she goes all "Shark Pool" on me.
开始向我介绍她的创业点子
Starts pitching her idea
如何打造一个环保有机且时髦的服装品牌
for a vegan, organic, hipster clothing line.
等下  她想让你投资她的服装品牌
Wait. She asked you to fund her clothing line?
玛格·戈尔本来要在节目上为服装做宣传的
Margo Gower was set to back it on the show.
奇怪就奇怪在这里
Well, that was the weird part.
我本来决定要投资
I was ready to offer her financing.
她在节目里攒下的人气
Her name recognition from the show
几乎能够保证收益
almost guarantees a profit.
可她又说
But then she says,
如果我辞演呢
"What if I were to leave the show?
这会影响你的决定吗
Would that make a difference?"
-她告诉你她可能会辞演  -对
- She told you that she might leave the show? - Yep.
然后我说
So I said,
亲爱的  这会大大影响我的决定
"Yes, sweetie, that would make a big difference."
没了节目  她的品牌分文不值
Without the show, her brand isn't worth jack.
为什么汉娜在即将得到
Why would Hannah suddenly want to leave the show
梦想的一切之后
after everything she ever dreamed of
会想要辞演
started happening for her?
不管发生了什么事  她显然都不想
Well, whatever was going on, she clearly wanted...
让其公之于众
to keep it under wraps.
巡警在调查中有新发现
Uniforms just got a hit on the canvass
一个卖卷饼的看到汉娜
from a pretzel vendor who saw Hannah
走进附近一栋大楼
walk into a nearby building
时间点就在绑架发生的时间范围内
right in our abduction time frame.
记录显示那栋大楼
Records show
是经过美国绿色建筑协会认证的建筑
it's L.E.E.D. certified green construction.
那栋大楼有亚龙木成分吗
Any evidence of alluaudia in the building?
我查过了
I checked.
墙纸里有
It's in the wallpaper.
她应该就在那栋楼里的某处被绑架过
She was held hostage someplace in that building.
找到这个地方
Find out where.
卡塞尔  我们走
Castle, let's go.
这就走
On my way.
你穿错西装了
Oh, you got the wrong blazer there.
没有  我们走
No, I don't. Let's go.
有事吗  卡塞尔先生
Is everything all right, Mr. Castle?
卡塞尔
Castle.
快
Come on.
没错  就是她
Yeah, that's definitely her.
你以前在这栋楼里见过她吗
Have you ever seen her in the building before?
不  只在那天晚上见过一次
Uh, no. It was just the one time the other night.
当时我在巡楼  看到她往29J走了
I was doing rounds when I saw her go into 29-J.
29J的户主是谁
And who owns 29-J?
海洋平台控股公司
Ocean Terrace Holdings. It's a corporation.
旗下有没有注册人名
Is there a name listed on it?
没有  现在有很多人都用
Uh, no. A lot of people buy units
公司的名字进行租赁  以保护隐私
under corporate names for privacy, so...
等等  你们听到了吗
Wait. Wait. Wait. Do you hear that?
好像有人在捶墙
Sounds like someone pounding on a wall.
佩内洛普
Penelope?
鲍勃
And Bob?!
你们俩又合
You two are back toge--
提示  有剧透
Spoiler alert.
鲍勃和佩内洛普在一起
Bob and Penelope together?
我简直不敢相信
I can't believe it.
就是说嘛
I know, right?
他俩对汉娜闭口不谈
Neither of them is talking about Hannah.
显然他俩除了滚床单之外
Well, clearly they have a lot more to hide
还有别的事情瞒着我们
than the fact that they were sleeping together.
这个故事转折点我可没猜到
Well, this is a plot twist I didn't see coming.
我查了一下那栋公寓
Hey, so I did some digging on the apartment.
海洋平台控股  是鲍勃的一个
Ocean Terrance Holdings, it's a shell company
空壳公司
owned by Bob.
是在他跟汉娜有外遇之后租下的
The lease began just after he and Hannah started their affair.
真奇怪
That's odd.
鲍勃离开佩内洛普之后
When Bob left Penelope,
他跟汉娜住进了汤姆森酒店
he moved into the Thompson Hotel with Hannah.
为什么还要租一个公寓
So why would he lease another apartment?
我查了佩内洛普的财产情况
I looked into Penelope's financials.
还记得汉娜每周五千块的收入吧
Remember those $5,000 payments that Hannah got?
这与佩内洛普从支票账户上
They line up exactly with withdrawals that Penelope made
支付的数额一样
from her checking account.
付钱给汉娜的人是佩内洛普
Penelope was paying hannah?
为什么
Wh-why would she do that?
除非她开口  否则我们没辙了
There's no way to know unless we get her to talk.
不好意思  你没看节目吗
I'm s--I'm sorry. Have you seen the show?
佩内洛普是强势的那一方
Penelope is the strong one.
想要知道实情
If anyone's gonna talk...
得问鲍勃
it's Bob.
可他也不说
But he's not.
我猜他定是害怕佩内洛普
And my guess is, he's afraid of Penelope.
看来是时候
Well, then perhaps it's time
按照佩内洛普的招数出手了
to tear a page from Penelope's play book.
拜托  你们不会是让我
Oh, come on. You guys aren't actually--
又不会少块肉
Couldn't hurt.
我都告诉你们  我没什么好
I told you, I have nothing to--
我说你可以讲话了吗
Did I say you could talk?
谁告诉你  你可以张开那张破嘴了
Did someone give you permission to open your sorry little mouth?
没人
No!
给我坐好  闭嘴  好好听着
So sit down, shut up, and listen.
我们知道公寓是你的  鲍勃
We know that apartment's yours, Bob.
我们知道汉娜曾经被困在那里
We know that Hannah was held hostage there,
也就是说
which means...
我可以用绑架罪名起诉你
I can nail you for kidnapping.
那足以让你蹲起码20年大牢
That's 20 years, easy.
-什么  不  我  -可我不会就此罢休
- What? No. I-- - But you know what? I'm not gonna stop there.
我要让你背上谋杀的罪名
I am going to fry you for murder.
等等  我  我没杀她
Wait. Me? I-I didn't kill her.
不许说谎
Don't lie to me!
你绑了她
You locked her up.
扣押她
You held her hostage.
有谁会对自己爱的人做这样的事
Who does that to someone that they love,
你这个满口谎言的...
you lying sack of...
我们没有相爱  好吧
We weren't in love, okay?!
这是个谎言  这件事都是
It was a lie. The whole thing was a lie.
我们没有交往过
There was no relationship.
汉娜跟我从来没有交往过
Hannah and I were never even together.
什么
What?!
我们为了收视率才那么说的
We only did it for the ratings.
收视率
The ratings?
阿什莉和斯通的订婚
Ashley and Stone's engagement
吸引了所有人的注意
was sucking up all the attention on the show.
佩内洛普的上镜时间在减少
Penelope's screen time was dropping,
这使她的服装销量锐减
which was killing her clothing sales.
她快疯了
She was out of her mind.
于是我们想出了一个计划
So we came up with a plan.
汉娜一开始不太情愿
Hannah was reluctant at first,
佩内洛普很有说服力
but Penelope can be pretty persuasive.
所以佩内洛普付给汉娜的五千美金
So the $5,000 that Penelope was paying Hannah,
是为了伪造你们的关系
that was to fake a relationship?
我们也没想到会这样
We never intended for it to end like this.
发生了什么  鲍勃
What happened, Bob?
那天晚上
The other night,
录完她的自白
after taping her confessional,
汉娜说她想谈谈
Hannah said she needed to talk.
但是不能让其他人看见我们三个在一起
Well, the three of us couldn't be seen together,
所以我们就约在了公寓
so we met at the apartment.
她告诉我们
She told us she couldn't bear
她不想再让别人认为她是第三者
everyone thinking she was this home wrecker.
她不能继续撒谎
She couldn't go on living a lie.
她说她要公开
Yeah, she said she was gonna go public,
揭露这段婚外情都是假的
reveal the affair had been faked all along.
这可是令人震惊的消息  你们做了什么
That's a pretty big bombshell. How'd you guys take it?
我们慌了神
How'd we take it? We panicked.
如果我们让她那么做
If we let her go through with it,
会毁了这部秀的
it would blow up the show.
没人会再相信我们
We'd lose all creditability.
也再没有人会买佩内洛普的衣服了
No one would buy Penelope's clothes anymore.
再说  我们违反了合同
Plus, we'd be in breach of contract
节目可以指控我们赔偿到倾家荡产
and the show could sue us for every cent we had.
我们的生活都会被毁了
Our whole lives would be ruined.
所以你们就把她绑了起来
So then you guys tied her up.
我们不知道该怎么做
We didn't know what to do.
就这么过了一天
So a whole day went by.
我们意识到不可能永远困着她
We realized we couldn't hold her forever s--
所以我们打了个电话
So we made a call.
打给谁了
So who'd you call?
鲍勃
Bob!
打给谁了
Who'd you call?
彼得·门罗
Peter Monroe.
《华尔街之妻》制作人
The "Wives of Wall Street" producer?
我们需要帮助
Yeah, we needed help.
这是他的节目  他和我们一样输不起
It's his show. He had as much to lose as we did.
你怎么跟他说的
What did you tell him?
一切
Everything.
然后他过来  让我和佩内洛普先走
Then he came over and told Penelope and me to leave,
他说他会处理汉娜的事
that he would handle Hannah.
我们以为他会晓之以情动之以理
We thought he was just gonna talk some sense into her,
也许给她涨工资啥的
you know, maybe sweeten her deal.
但是接下来我们听到的消息
But the next thing we knew,
是汉娜死了
Hannah was dead.
抱歉  先生  我已经尽力阻止他们了
I'm so sorry, sir. I tried to stop them.
-杰夫  出去  -好
- Jeff, get outta here. - Right.
门罗先生  你是不是患有
Mr. Monroe, are you pathologically incapable
病态说谎症
of telling the truth?
这个要看情况  什么事
Well, that depends. What's this about?
你在汉娜谋杀案中扮演的角色
Your role in Hannah's murder.
她的死跟我一点关系都没有
Whoa. I had nothing to do with her murder.
鲍勃认为是你做的
Bob thinks you did.
我们知道在汉娜死前  他在公寓
We know about him calling you from the apartment
给你打电话说明了她的情况
about Hannah just before she died.
好吧  佩内洛普和鲍勃打给我了
Okay, Penelope and Bob called me.
一对傻瓜
Couple of moron idiots...
那样挟持着她
Taking her hostage like that.
这么说你去了
So you went over there?
我当然去了
Of course I went over there.
我从那两个疯子手里救了她
Hell, I saved her from those two lunatics.
我可是好人
I'm the good guy.
你们知道我去做了什么吗
You know what I did when I got there?
我放她走了  要水吗
I let her go. Water?
要的
Please.
如果汉娜曝光婚外情是假的
Look, if Hannah exposed that your main storyline was faked,
你的节目就会一落千丈
your show would go down in flames.
粉丝们会大怒
The fans would be outraged.
我就很愤怒
Hell, I'm outraged.
我试着阻止她
I was trying to stop her.
我打算给她更多的钱  以她为主角开发新剧
I offered Hannah more money, her own series,
给她想要的一切
anything she wanted
只要她闭上嘴
to not blow the lid off the show.
我是说
I mean...
她会毁了一切
She was gonna ruin everything.
我求她留下
I begged her to stay.
我跟着她  提供给她我能给予的一切提议
I followed her out and gave her every decent pitch I had.
但是她不同意
But she wouldn't deal.
她坐进出租车  那之后我就没见过她
She got into a taxi, and I never saw her again.
有个更好的版本
Here's a better story--
你抓起一把刀  跟着她
You grabbed a knife and you followed her.
不  我没有  我发誓
No, I didn't. I swear.
我去了玩家俱乐部
I went straight to the player's club,
点了几杯鸡尾酒
ordered a couple of cocktails,
等着我的世界开始崩落
and waited for my world to start to cave in.
但是什么事也没发生
But nothing happened.
第二天早上  我得知她死了
Next morning, I found out that she was dead.
玩家俱乐部的经理证实
So the manager at the player's club confirms
门罗从晚上十点直到午夜后
that Monroe was there from 10:00 p.m.
都在那里
till well after midnight.
他不是凶手
He's not our guy.
那就只剩玛格了
Which leaves Margo,
因为汉娜后来去了那里  但是
because that's where Hannah went next, but...
在被挟持那么久之后
after being held hostage
还提出辞演
and demanding to leave the show,
我很怀疑她会重新回去工作
I doubt she went there to recommit to the job.
玛格之前一定骗了我们
Margo had to have been lying to us.
玛格的确说谎了
Margo was lying, all right.
她告诉你们那天晚上她放汉娜进了楼
She told you she buzzed up Hannah that night, right?
那不可能
That's impossible.
那楼里的安保系统连着她的手机
The buzzer on the building connects through her phone.
根据电话记录
According to the phone records,
汉娜是9:57进到楼里的
Hannah was buzzed up at 9:57 p.m.
根据玛格的财务记录
Well, according to Margo's financials,
几乎在同时  9:58
at almost exactly the same time, 9:58 p.m.,
她在几个街区外的
she was using her credit card
洛伦佐熟食店使用信用卡
at Lorenzo's deli ten blocks away.
谢谢  埃斯波
Thanks, Espo.
玛格要好好解释一番了
Margo's got some explaining to do.
如果她没让汉娜进门  那谁开门了
If she didn't buzz Hannah in, then who did?
她为什么要说谎呢
And why would she lie about it?
卡塞尔  你今天和盖茨怎么了
Castle, what's going on with you and Gates today?
什么意思
What do you mean?
说真的  卡塞尔
Seriously, Castle,
你在想什么呢
what were you thinking?
我想要给你个惊喜
Well, I wanted to surprise you.
把我的礼物放在盖茨的上衣里吗
By putting my gift in Gates' blazer?
好吧  我被惊到了
Okay, I'm surprised.
为什么你和盖茨要穿相似的上衣呢
Well, why do you and Gates have to wear such similar blazers?
你留条了吗
Did you write a note?
我当然留条了啊  我可是作家
Of course I wrote a note. I'm a writer.
情话吗
Was it romantic?
情人节礼物  所以  当然是情话
It's Valentine's Day, so, yeah, it was romantic.
你写我名字了吗
Did you put my name on it?
天呐  卡塞尔  拜托  写我名字了吗
Oh, god, Castle, please. Did you put my name on it?
我不记得了
I can't remember.
我写了自己名字  我只记得这么多
I put my name on it. I know that much.
要是盖茨发现我们在交往
If Gates finds out that we're dating,
那就完了
then that's it.
我们就不能一起工作了
We're not gonna be working together anymore.
所以说我再努力拿回来嘛
Why do you think I've been trying so hard to get it back?
我们会拿回来的
Oh, we will get it back,
一回到警局就去拿
right when we get to the precinct.
但现在我们有谋杀案要破
But right now we got a murder to solve.
也许是最后一案
Maybe our last.
请进
Come in.
谢谢你让我们进来
Thanks for buzzing us in.
有什么我能做的吗
What can I do for you?
你知道这栋楼有趣的一点就是
You know, the interesting thing about this building
与你手机相连接的大门保安系统
is that the buzzer system runs through your telephone.
然后呢
So?
每次有访客获准进入
So anytime someone gets buzzed up,
手机就会把时间记录下来
it gets time stamped.
既然我们知道你在洛伦佐熟食店购物
And since we know you were at Lorenzo's deli buying onions,
你不可能在凶案发生当晚
you couldn't have buzzed Hannah up
放汉娜进入大楼
the night of the murder.
这意味着放她进来的另有其人
Which means somebody else did.
你为什么要对我们撒谎
Why did you lie to us?
看了节目  我知道
From watching the show, I know that
你的丈夫在布鲁塞尔谈生意
your husband is in Brussels working on a deal.
不可能是他
So it couldn't have been him,
那就只剩下一个人
which leaves only one other person living in this house.
你的儿子斯通
Your son Stone.
他和汉娜一起工作  对吗
He worked with Hannah, didn't he?
我不喜欢你的言外之意
I don't like what you're implying.
他们之间有矛盾吗
Were they having problems with each other?
斯通在哪里  戈尔太太
Where is Stone right now, Ms. Gower?
我又不知道  他都是成年人了
I don't know. He's an adult.
是吗  因为在第三季第五集里
Really? Because in Season Three, Episode Five,
你说你是你儿子的看护人
You said that you are your son's keeper,
永远知道他在哪  在做什么
always knowing where he is and what he's doing.
看起来有人做好了功课
Looks like one of us did their homework.
戈尔太太  斯通在哪
Now, Ms. Gower, where is Stone?
我想和我的律师谈谈
I would like to talk to my attorney.
娱乐律师还是刑事律师
Entertainment or criminal?
长官  我们找到他了
Yeah. Sir, we got him.
他要去哪里
Where's he headed?
斯通买了一张去布宜诺斯艾利斯的单程票
Stone bought a one-way ticket to Buenos Aires.
飞机一小时内起飞
Flight departs in an hour.
鲍勃和佩内洛普假装分手
Bob and Penelope fake their breakup,
而现在无邪的斯通成了凶手
and now poor sweet innocent Stone's a killer?
真人秀上还有真的吗
Is there anything real on that reality show?
看节目时我的头疼可是真的
Just the headache I get when I watch it.
通知运输安全局
Call T.S.A.
别让他登机
Do not let him get on that flight.
老天
Oh, my... god.
为什么突然要去阿根廷  斯通
Why the sudden trip to Argentina, Stone?
我只是需要点儿时间静静
I just needed a little time away.
我们知道在被害的当晚
We know that Hannah showed up at your apartment
汉娜出现在你家
the night that she was killed,
我们也知道你让她进门了
and we know that you let her in.
但因为某些原因
And then for some reason,
你的妈妈却对此撒谎
your mother lied about it.
她为什么这么做
Now why would she do that?
是因为汉娜告诉你
Was it because Hannah told you
她要毁了节目
that she was gonna blow up the show
然后你突然看到自己梦想的
and you suddenly saw your dreams
阿什莉/斯通衍生剧就要灰飞烟灭
of an Ashley/Stone spin-off going out the window?
这是你妈妈撒谎的原因吗
Is that why your mom lied?
就因为你尾随汉娜出了门
'cause you followed Hannah out of the apartment
然后杀了她
and you killed her?
我没有杀她
I didn't kill her.
你们不明白吗
Don't you guys get it?
我爱上了她
I was in love with her.
哇  爱
Whoa. Love?
那阿什莉呢
What about Ashley?
那是我妈妈的主意
That was my mom's idea.
我喜欢阿什
Look, I like Ash.
我们从小就认识
We've known each other since we were kids.
但是
But...
之后我遇见了汉娜
Then I met Hannah.
我们被迫成戴上假面
We bonded over being forced into things
我们同病相怜
that weren't really us.
还有人知道你们之间的事吗
Did anyone else know about the two of you?
没有
No.
坦白我们的关系风险太大
There's too much at stake.
过去的几周
For the past few weeks,
汉娜忍无可忍
Hannah just couldn't take it anymore,
节目对她和家庭产生了致命的影响
what the show was doing to her, her family.
她在寻找一条出路
She was looking for a way out.
我们都是
We both were.
但是谎言
But the lies had just...
越说越大
gotten so big--
她的假婚外情  我的订婚
Her fake affair, my engagement.
我妈妈和阿什
Ash and my mom...
她们一直惦记着衍生剧
They were counting on that spin-off.
汉娜去找你那晚究竟发生了什么
What happened the night that Hannah showed up?
她很激动
She was hysterical.
她说想现在就离开
She said she wanted to leave town right away,
机不可失  时不再来
That it was now or never.
我也打算走  但是
And I was going to, but...
但是怎么了
But what?
我妈妈回家了
Then my mom came home.
她发现了我们的关系
When she found out about our relationship,
她发疯了
She went crazy.
她把汉娜赶了出去
She threw Hannah out.
但是最糟的是
But the worst part...
汉娜求我
was that Hannah begged me
和她一起走
to go with her.
但是我没有
But I couldn't.
在她需要我
In the moment when she needed me
反抗我妈妈的时候
to stand up to my mother...
我没有
I couldn't.
斯通
Stone...
你妈妈去追她了吗
Did your mother go after her?
没有
No.
汉娜一走
As soon as Hannah left,
我就知道自己铸成了大错
I knew I'd made a mistake.
所以我就追她到了街上
So I ran out to catch up with her in the street.
然后吻了她
And I kissed her.
我告诉她我爱她
And I told her I loved her.
但是她说为时已晚
But she said it was too late...
她再也不想见到我和我妈妈
that she never wanted to see any of us again.
有人能证明你在哪吗
Can anyone verify your whereabouts
在你和汉娜分开之后
after you and Hannah went your separate ways?
我独自散步  所以  没人
I took a long walk, so, no.
你怎么看  你相信他吗
So what do you think? You believe him?
他有动机  她离开了他
He had motive. She was leaving him.
而且他也是最后一个见到她活着的人
And he was the last one to see her alive
离她被害的地方只有一街区之遥  所以
A block away from where she was killed, so...
唯一的问题就是
only problem is,
我们没有任何证据
We don't have any proof.
我们无法把斯通和犯罪现场联系起来
We can't tie Stone to the crime scene.
其实  我们可以
Actually, we can.
我凭着直觉查了他的新婚礼物清单
On a hunch, I took a look at his wedding registry.
阿什莉和斯通收到
It turns out that Ashley and Stone are registered
一套高原刀具
for a set of Takahara V.G. Knives,
包括三周前运到的
Including the 240 millimeter,
24厘米的刀具
which shipped out three weeks ago.
实验报告确实说那是一把新刀
The lab report did say that it was a new knife.
那就可以结案了
Then that seals it.
不  不一定
No, not necessarily.
我们忘了婚礼礼仪
We're forgetting wedding etiquette.
礼物不是送去给新郎的
The gifts don't go to the groom.
谢谢你来  阿什莉
Thank you for coming, Ashley.
能帮上忙就好
Oh, anything I can do to help.
你现在一定正忙着策划婚礼
You must be so busy planning for the wedding right now
处理所有新婚礼物
and dealing with all of the gifts.
对的
Oh, yeah.
我们知道你的表妹
Well, we know that your cousin
送给了一套高原刀具
bought you that set of Takahara V.G. Knives,
就是礼品清单上那一套
The ones that you have on your registry.
好吧
Okay.
有意思的是
The funny thing is,
当我们去你家时
when we went to your apartment,
你偏偏少了那把24厘米的刀具
you don't have the 240 millimeter.
她竟然没送你一整套
And isn't just a little weird
是不是有点可疑
that she wouldn't get you the whole set?
你们去了我家
You were in my apartment?
对  我们也去了你的陶瓷工作室
Yeah, we also went to your ceramic studio as well.
顺便说一句  你的作品很出色
Ah, your work is lovely, by the way.
釉彩的颜色光辉夺目
The colors of your glazes are stunning.
我是说要很费力才能
I mean, it must take a lot of work to get--
让成品完美无缺  要用化学品什么的
to get them just right, like chemicals.
比如说
Like the, um,
我们找到的氧化锑
antimony oxide we found, for example.
那是干什么用的
What is that for?
是遮光剂  能够是物件不透明
It's an opacifier. It makes things opaque.
不过这反倒是让我们的案子明净起来
Only in this case, it seems to make things clear.
我们在汉娜谋杀案中的凶器上
The knife that was used in Hannah's murder,
发现了氧化锑残留
we found traces of antimony oxide on it
你是留下的
from you.
不
No.
你在手机上收到了粉丝站的提示  对吧
You got an alert on your phone from the fan site, didn't you?
汉娜在斯通公寓的那张照片
That photo of Hannah at Stone's apartment--
你已经有所怀疑
I mean, you already had your suspicions.
如今噩梦成真了
You just confirmed your worst fears.
不不
No. No.
我不想谈了  我要走了
I think we're done here. I'm gonna go.
借过
Excuse me.
借过  我...得找到我的钥匙
Excuse me. I've just-- let me find my keys
然后我就走
And I will go.
好吧
Fine!
我有所怀疑
I had my suspicions.
看到照片后  我抓起刀
And when I saw that picture, I grabbed the knife,
想吓吓她
just to scare her.
我到了那之后  斯通在亲吻她
But when I got there, Stone was kissing her
对她说他爱她
and saying he loved her.
我不能让她夺走我的未婚夫
I couldn't just let her steal my fiance.
我们的衍生剧正在进行最后的商议
Our spin-off was in final negotiations,  for god sakes.
于是
So...
在斯通走后
when Stone left,
我跟踪了汉娜
I followed Hannah.
消灭了威胁
I put an end to the threat.
下一代《华尔街之妻》
The next generation of "The Wives of Wall Street,"
和阿什莉真是把抓马升级了啊
and Ashley takes it to a whole new level.
或许她只是在循序自己的座右铭吧
Well, maybe she was just following their motto--
"不要让任何人阻止你得到想要的东西"
"Don't let anyone stop you from getting what you want."
弄得好像
As if being on TV
上了电视她就不会自食其果了
somehow made her immune to the consequences.
至少我们可以告诉汉娜的家人
You know, at least we can tell Hannah's family
婚外情是假的
that the affair wasn't real,
她打算回家
that she was actually planning on going home.
说到后果
Speaking of consequences...
为什么盖茨一声不吭
why hasn't Gates said anything yet?
不知道
Yeah, I don't know.
她要么是打算置之不理
Maybe she's choosing to ignore it
要么是像鲨鱼一样等待时机
or just biding her time like a shark.
晚安  伙计们
Night, guys.
情人节快乐
Happy Valentine's Day.
继续大战五十回合吗
Ah, once more onto the breach?
事实上  珍妮给我发短信了
Uh, actually, Jenny just texted me,
今晚我可以养精蓄锐了
and I have the night off.
不过我们还是会...
I mean, we'll probably still,
你们懂的
uh, you know,
不过今晚是为了浪漫
but tonight it will be for romantic reasons.
是啊
Yeah.
埃斯波
Hey, Espo.
你的女伴来了
Your date's here.
我就知道他们有约
I knew they had plans.
你知道却不告诉我
You knew they had plans and you didn't tell me?
因为她要我保密
Yeah, because she asked me to keep it a secret.
这对他们来说很重要
This is a really big deal for them.
她不想让你吐槽他们
She doesn't want you making fun of 'em.
我才不...是啊
I wouldn't make fun-- no, that's...
铁定的
that's not true. That'd be fish in a barrel.
蕾妮
Lanie...
你美呆了
You look great.
不会太过火吗
Yeah? It's not too much?
不会  不过对卡塞尔来说有点过火
No. It might be a little too much for Castle.
-眼睛抬起来  哥们  -了解
- Eyes up, bud. - I do.
你光彩照人  蕾妮
You look amazing, Lanie.
谢谢  哈维
Thanks, Javi.
有什么安排
So what's the plan?
在熔炉餐厅定了位
Uh, reservations at Le Fourneau.
法国菜
French?
我爱法国菜[法语]
I love french.
我知道  小美人
Je le sais, ma petite jolie.
-回见  -回见
- Au revoir. - Au revoir.
情人节的魔力降临了
Ah, the magic of Valentine's Day is upon us.
卡塞尔先生
Mr. Castle.
来我办公室  现在
My office, now.
又没了
And there it goes.
你真的认为
Did you really think
我
that I, of all people,
会认同这件事吗
would be okay with this?
不  我
No, I...
以为
Thought--I...
你集美丽  热情
"You are beauty, passion,
与傲人的智慧于一身
"and fierce intellect.
做我的情人吧  里克
Be my Valentine. Rick."
我只写了这些吗
Is that all I wrote in there?
这还不够吗
Isn't that enough?
你到底怎么回事
What the hell is wrong with you?
我都结婚了
I'm a married woman.
我知道  我只是在想
N--I-I know. No, I know. I just thought--
这不会是你拙劣的把戏
Is this some lame, harebrained scheme
想得到我的认可吧
to garner favor with me?
是的
Yeah.
就是这样
That's--that's what this is.
你这是自取其辱
Well, it backfired.
我会忘掉这件事
And I am willing to forget that this ever happened
如果你保证控制你顽童般的行为
if you assure me that you can tame your childish nonsense
对我尊重点
and accord me some respect.
我会的
I-I will. I can. I will.
现在我要回家了
And now I will go home
回到我丈夫身边
to my husband,
因为
because...
我是他的情人
I'm his Valentine.
反正她之前就不喜欢你  卡塞尔
But she already hated you, Castle.
情况也差不到哪去
So it doesn't sound like you're any worse off.
不过我很佩服她处理这事的方式
I do respect the way she handled it, though--
强势而有决断力
Strong, decisive.
我觉得
I feel like somehow,
这让我们更亲密了
it brought us closer.
耳环的事我很遗憾
I am sorry about the earrings, though.
是啊  它们太耀眼了
Yeah, me, too. They were... stunning.
我会再送一份
I will get you something else
更美的
even more beautiful.
这次我要试着不把礼物送给别的女人
I'll just try not to give it to another woman first.
那样最好
Oh, that would be nice.
提到这个
Which reminds me...?
你送我什么
What did you get me?
打开
Open it.
也许在另一个抽屉里
Maybe it's in another drawer.
是抽屉
It is the drawer.
你的抽屉
It's your drawer.
虽说不是光剑  但
I-I mean, I know it's not a light saber, but--
不
No.
完美极了
It's perfect.
情人节快乐
Happy Valentine's Day.
现在
Now...
脱掉你的衣服
take your clothes off,
放进你的抽屉里
put them in your drawer,
我们床上见
and meet me in the bed.
不是吧
Seriously?